Eugenics Record Office Records 1670-1964 Mss.Ms.Coll.77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Trait Files, 1670-1964 (Box Series I: 1-65)
  - A:0533:94 - A:053084 (Box Series I-14)
    - One-Egg Twins: Placental Circulation, 1896-1913; A:0533:96122 (Box Series I-14)
    - Tubal Twin Pregnancy--One Egg, 1903-1911; A:0533:9626 (Box Series I-14)
    - Hydramnios, 1882-1921; A:05332 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins with Single Amnion, 1886-1927; A:05336 (Box Series I-14)
    - Blighted Twin Fetus, 1819-1920; A:05337 #1 (Box Series I-14)
    - Blighted Twin Fetus, 1716-1925; A:05337 #2 (Box Series I-14)
    - Freemartins, 1910-1916; A:053002 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twinning in Birds, 1903; A:0530028 (Box Series I-14)
    - Statistics on Twins, 1933; A:053003 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twinning: Legal Aspects, 1902; A:053007 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Repeating, 1921-1930; A:05301 #1 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins Development, 1865-1919; A:05301 #2 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Abnormal Development, 1904; A:053:015 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins: Superfoetation, 1921; A:05302 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Stature, 1874-1925; A:053:02 (Box Series I-14)
    - Plural Birth in Animals, 1861-1910; A:0530029 #1 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Living Mammals, n.d.; A:053029 #2 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Superimpregnation, 1828-1924; A:05303 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Two Ova to the Follicle, 1894; A:05304 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Bicornate, 1894-1925; A:05344 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Fecundity, 1823-1919; A:053:05 (Box Series I-14)
    - 1923, [A:053:051] (Box Series I-14)
    - Twinning-Size of Family, 1897-1912; A:053:051 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Fecundity of the Mother, 1869, n.d.; A:053:052 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twinning Families, 1869-1905; A:053:053 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Longevity, 1915; A:053:077 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Disease, 1924-1931; A:053:08 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins: Miscellaneous Clinical Histories, 1841-1919; A:05308 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins: Placental Praevia, 1895-1919; A:053081 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twins--Locked, 1861-1919; A:053082 (Box Series I-14)
    - Inter- and Extra-Uterine Twin Pregnancy, 1878-1919; A:053083 (Box Series I-14)
    - Twinning--Intermittant, 1842-1921; A:053084 (Box Series I-14)
  - A:053:127 - A:0537 #5 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Freckles, 1926; A:053:127 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Fingerprints, 1934; A:053:131 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins: Polymastia, 1903; A:053:16624 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Naevus, 1872-1927; A:053.1938 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Skin Diseases, 1926; A:053:199 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins: Polydactylism, 1841; A:053:2106 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Hydrocephalus, 1910; A:053:221 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Amentia, 1862-1919; A:053:313 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Idiocy, 1876; A:053:3131 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twinning--Amaurotic Idiocy, 1919; A:053:31321 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Mongolian Idiocy, 1899-1929; A:053.31322 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twinning--Epilepsy, 1910-1919; A:053:314 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Insanity, 1863-1910; A:053.316 #1 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Insanity, 1886-1925; A:053.316 #2 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins: Dementia Praecox, 1926; A:053:3162 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins: Manic-Depressive Insanity, 1935; A:053:3164 (Box Series I-15)
    - Psychoses in Twins, 1888-1915; A:053.317 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twinning: Cerebrum, 1908; A:053:32 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Paralysis, 1888; A:053:341 (Box Series I-15)
    - Hemiplegia in Identical Twins, 1924; A:053:3414 (Box Series I-15)
    - Nervous and Mental Disease in Twins, 1952; A:053.38 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Mental Traits, n.d.; A:053.4 (Box Series I-15)
    - Blighted Acardia--Twins, 1890-1919; A:053372 (Box Series I-15)
    - Hydatid Mole--Twins, 1909-1910; A:053375 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins: Congential Deformity, 1794-1900; A:053378 (Box Series I-15)
    - Two Egg Twins, 1808-1910; A:0534 (Box Series I-15)
    - Two-Egg Twins: Dropsy, 1902; A:0534:086 (Box Series I-15)
    - Two Egg Twins: Tubal Pregnancy, 1905-1919; A:0534:9626 (Box Series I-15)
    - Twins--Blighted Two Egg Fetus, 1832-1921; A:05347 (Box Series I-15)
    - Cosmobia, 1905; A:0536 (Box Series I-15)
    - Triplets--Clippings, 1916-1935; A:0537 #1 (Box Series I-15)
    - Triplets, 1844-1921; A:0537 #2 (Box Series I-15)
    - Triplets, 1838-1920; A:0537 #3 (Box Series I-15)
    - Triplets, 1724-1920; A:0537 #4 (Box Series I-15)
    - Triplets [ includes photos], 1933; A:0537 #5 (Box Series I-15)
  - A:0537 #6 - A:0539 #2 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets, 1919-1929; A:0537 #6 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets, 1865-1926; A:0537 #7 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets: Monstrosities, 1898; A:0537:0531 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets: Tubal Gestation, 1902; A:0537:9626 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets, 1841-1920; A:053712 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets: All Uniovular, 1889-1923; A:053713 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets: Triovular, 1844-1920; A:053714 (Box Series I-16)
    - Repeating, 1863-1920; A:053715 (Box Series I-16)
    - 1878, A:053716 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplet: Blighted Fetus, 1818-1920; A:053717 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets: Clinical Histories, 1833-1920; A:053718 (Box Series I-16)
    - Triplets: Hydramnios, 1890; A:05372 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quadruplets--Clippings, 1920-1935; A:05374 #1 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quadruplets, 1790-1920; A:05374 #2 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quadruplets [ contains Davenport correspondence], 1924-1933; A:05374 #3 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quadruplets--Triovular, 1842-1920; A:053744 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quadruplets--Clinical History, 1847-1885; A:053748 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quintuplets--Dionne Clippings, 1934-1936; A:05375 #1 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quintuplets, 1787-1920; A:05375 #2 (Box Series I-16)
    - Quintuplets [ contains Davenport correspondence], 1919-1922; A:05375 #3 (Box Series I-16)
    - Sextuplets or More, 1862-1933; A:05376 (Box Series I-16)
    - Twins: Late Pregnancy vs. Precocious, 1889-1922; A:0538 (Box Series I-16)
    - Sex Rates, 1923-1930; A:0539 #1 (Box Series I-16)
    - Sex Ratio, 1912-1930; A:0539 #2 (Box Series I-16)
  - A:053973 - A:077 #1 (Box Series I-17)
    - 1920, A:053973 (Box Series I-17)
    - Many Descendants, 1896-1919; A:055 (Box Series I-17)
    - Mating, 1912-1920; A:06 (Box Series I-17)
    - Mate Selection, 1862-1934; A:061 (Box Series I-17)
    - Study on Consanguinity Made by William F. Blades, 1913; A:062 #1 (Box Series I-17)
    - Consanguinity, 1914-1930; A:062 #2 (Box Series I-17)
    - Consanguineous Marriage, 1911-1919; A:0621 (Box Series I-17)
    - Half Sibs, n.d.; A:0622 (Box Series I-17)
    - Cousin Marriages, 1919-1928; A:0626 (Box Series I-17)
    - First Cousin Marriages, 1913-1920; A:0627 (Box Series I-17)
    - Second Cousins Marriages, 1919; A:0629 (Box Series I-17)
    - Plural Matings Yielding Children, 1935; A:063 (Box Series I-17)
    - Serial Marriages, 1930; A:0633 and 0634 (Box Series I-17)
    - Differential Mating, 1913; A:064 (Box Series I-17)
    - Vitality, 1912-1930; A:07 #1 (Box Series I-17)
    - Vitality, 1912-1914; A:07 #2 (Box Series I-17)
    - Stillbirths, 1906; A:072 (Box Series I-17)
    - Infant Deaths, 1910-1934; A:075 #1 (Box Series I-17)
    - Infant Mortality, 1912; A:075 #2 (Box Series I-17)
    - Longevity [ contains correspondence of Davenport and J. Alden Mason], 1917-1933; A:077 #1 (Box Series I-17)
  - A:077 #2 - A:0826 #1 (Box Series I-18)
    - Longevity, 1916-1933; A:077 #2 (Box Series I-18)
    - Longevity--Great, 1935; A:0772 (Box Series I-18)
    - Longevity--Athletes, 1928; A:077·459 (Box Series I-18)
    - Longevity (Extreme), 1912-1919; A:0776 (Box Series I-18)
    - Defects in Vitality, 1919; A:0779 (Box Series I-18)
    - General Disease, 1924-1935; A:08 #1 (Box Series I-18)
    - General Disease, 1921-1922; A:08 #2 (Box Series I-18)
    - General Disease, [1921-1922]; A:08 #3 (Box Series I-18)
    - General Disease, [1921-1922]; A:08 #4 (Box Series I-18)
    - Incidence of General Diseases to Build, 1921-1922; A:08 #5 (Box Series I-18)
    - Immunity, 1916-1926; A:08003 (Box Series I-18)
    - Typhoid Fever, 1925; A:0801 (Box Series I-18)
    - Malaria, 1919; A:0804 (Box Series I-18)
    - Smallpox, 1934; A:0805 (Box Series I-18)
    - Scarlet Fever, 1924-1925; A:0807 (Box Series I-18)
    - Diphtheria, 1924; A:0809 (Box Series I-18)
    - Influenza, 1919; A:0810 (Box Series I-18)
    - Dysentery, 1934; A:0814 (Box Series I-18)
    - Leprosy, 1887-1920; A:0817 (Box Series I-18)
    - Chicken Pox, 1930; A:08191 (Box Series I-18)
    - Abscess, 1921; A:08201 (Box Series I-18)
    - Pellagra, 1913-1926; A:0826 #1 (Box Series I-18)
  - A:0826 #2 - A:084 #2 (Box Series I-19)
    - Pellagra: Reprints, 1914-1917; A:0826 #2 (Box Series I-19)
    - Pellagra, n.d.; A:0826 #3 (Box Series I-19)
    - Exudative Diathesis, 1909-1910; A:08262 (Box Series I-19)
    - Tuberculosis, 1907-1913; A:083 #1 (Box Series I-19)
    - Tuberculosis, 1912-1934; A:083 #2 (Box Series I-19)
    - Tuberculosis, 1921; A:083 #3 (Box Series I-19)
    - Tuberculosis-Pulmonary, 1912-1922; A:08311 (Box Series I-19)
    - Lupus (Skin Tuberculosis), n.d.; A:08315 (Box Series I-19)
    - Tuberculosis of Joints, 1920; A:0833 (Box Series I-19)
    - Rickets, 1913-1925; A:0836 (Box Series I-19)
    - Syphilis, 1911-1930; A:0837 (Box Series I-19)
    - Cancer, 1901-1916; A:084 #1 (Box Series I-19)
    - Cancer, 1911-1912; A:084 #2 (Box Series I-19)
  - A:084 #3 - A:08505 #2 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer, 1908-1934; A:084 #3 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer, 1866-1930; A:084 #4 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer, 1911, n.d.; A:084 #5 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer (not complete), 1914-1923; A:084 #6 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer, 1910-1911; A:084 #7 (Box Series I-20)
    - Stomach, Liver, Pylorus, n.d.; A:08412 (Box Series I-20)
    - Intestinal Cancer, 1925; A:08414 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer of Peritoneum, 1926; A:08415 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer of the Female Genital Organs, 1919-1922; A:0842 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer of Breast, 1934; A:0843 (Box Series I-20)
    - Cancer--Face, 1919; A:0846 (Box Series I-20)
    - Tumors, 1913-1930; A:0849 (Box Series I-20)
    - Lymphosarcoma, 1921; A:0849.85 (Box Series I-20)
    - Tumor of Spleen (Gaucher's Disease), 1926-1930; A:084986 (Box Series I-20)
    - Rheumatism, 1919-1935; A:0850 (Box Series I-20)
    - Arthritis, 1908-1935; A:08502 (Box Series I-20)
    - Gout, 1909-1919; A:08503 (Box Series I-20)
    - Scurvy, 1920; A:08504 (Box Series I-20)
    - Diabetes Mellitus, 1865-1931; A:08505 #1 (Box Series I-20)
    - Diabetes--Pedigrees from Files (L. Burt), 1931; A:08505 #2 (Box Series I-20)
  - A:08505 #3 - A:0921 (Box Series I-21)
    - Diabetes Mellitus, 1930-1934; A:08505 #3 (Box Series I-21)
    - Diabetes--Insipidus, 1877-1933; A:08506 (Box Series I-21)
    - Glycosuria, 1929-1935; A:08507 (Box Series I-21)
    - Pentosuria, 1923; A:08508 (Box Series I-21)
    - Exophthalmic Goiter, 1918-1932; A:0851 (Box Series I-21)
    - Addison's Disease, Bronze Disease, 1922; A:0852 (Box Series I-21)
    - Leukemia (Hodgkin's Disease), 1847-1931; A:0853 (Box Series I-21)
    - Erythemia, 1917; A:08534 (Box Series I-21)
    - Anemia, 1901-1934; A:0854 (Box Series I-21)
    - Haemolytic Anemia, 1926; A:08541 (Box Series I-21)
    - Pernicious Anemia, 1900-1926; A:08542 (Box Series I-21)
    - Splenic Anemia, 1914-1926; A:08543 (Box Series I-21)
    - Polycythaemia, 1924; A:08545 (Box Series I-21)
    - Toxemia--Infectious Fevers, 1920; A:0855 (Box Series I-21)
    - Alcoholism, 1879-1933; A:0856 #1 (Box Series I-21)
    - Alcoholism, 1886-1925; A:0856 #2 (Box Series I-21)
    - Narcosis, 1924; A:0859 (Box Series I-21)
    - Oedema, 1907-1925; A:086 (Box Series I-21)
    - Milroy's Disease, 1917-1928; A:0861 (Box Series I-21)
    - Other General Diseases, n.d.; A:088 (Box Series I-21)
    - Other General Defects, 1935; A:089 (Box Series I-21)
    - Farmers and Planters, 1925-1935; A:0911 (Box Series I-21)
    - Gardeners, Florists, 1911; A:0912 (Box Series I-21)
    - Stock Raisers, 1910; A:0916 (Box v, Box Series I-21)
    - Professional Service, 1921; A:092 (Box Series I-21)
    - Entertainers, 1922; A:0921 (Box Series I-21)
  - A:09211 #1 - A:09238 (Box Series I-22)
    - Actors, 1908-1911; A:09211 #1 (Box Series I-22)
    - Actors, 1909-1912; A:09211 #2 (Box Series I-22)
    - Actors, 1908-1912; A:09211 #3 (Box Series I-22)
    - Actors, 1916-1930; A:09211 #4 (Box Series I-22)
    - Showmen, 1921-1930; A:09212 (Box Series I-22)
    - Theatrical Managers, 1910-1911; A:[09]213-aaa (Box Series I-22)
    - Instrumental Musicians, 1934-1935; A:09214 (Box Series I-22)
    - Orchestra Conductors, 1920; A:[09]2141-aaa (Box Series I-22)
    - Singers, 1909-1913; A:[09]215-aaa (Box Series I-22)
    - Dancers, 1911; A:[09]216-aaa (Box Series I-22)
    - Jockeys, 1929; A:09217 (Box Series I-22)
    - Artists, 1910-1925; A:0922 (Box Series I-22)
    - Designers, 1920; A:09222 (Box Series I-22)
    - Sketch Artists, 1907-1923; A:09223 (Box Series I-22)
    - Painters, 1909-1910; A:[09]224-aaa (Box Series I-22)
    - Sculptors, 1914-1917; A:09225 (Box Series I-22)
    - Medical [ contains Laughlin correspondence], 1918-1931; A:0923 (Box Series I-22)
    - Physicians, 1918-1934; A:09231 (Box Series I-22)
    - Dermatologist, 1926; A:092312 (Box Series I-22)
    - Dentists, 1925; A:09238 (Box Series I-22)
  - A:0924 - A:09293 #1 (Box Series I-23)
    - Engineers, 1911-1935; A:0924 (Box Series I-23)
    - Military, n.d.; A:092432 (Box Series I-23)
    - Aviators, 1908-1928; A:092433 (Box Series I-23)
    - Automobilists, 1910; A:092434 (Box Series I-23)
    - Inventors, 1928; A:09248 (Box Series I-23)
    - Lawyers and Politicians, 1090-1911; A:0925 #1 (Box Series I-23)
    - Lawyers and Politicians, 1909-1911; A:0925 #2 (Box Series I-23)
    - Orators, 1911; A:09253 (Box Series I-23)
    - Judges, 1910-1911; A:09254 (Box Series I-23)
    - Literary, n.d.; A:0926 (Box Series I-23)
    - Authors, 1906-1912; A:09261 (Box Series I-23)
    - Journalists, 1915-1933; A:09262 (Box Series I-23)
    - Publishers, 1912; A:092621 (Box Series I-23)
    - Clergymen, 1907-1933; A:0927 (Box Series I-23)
    - Missionaries, 1916-1934; A:09271 (Box Series I-23)
    - Evangelists, 1910; A:09275 (Box Series I-23)
    - Gamblers, n.d.; A:09290 (Box Series I-23)
    - Adventurers, 1906-1935; A:092901 (Box Series I-23)
    - Executives, 1910-1920; A:09291 (Box Series I-23)
    - Reformers, 1910-1920; A:09292 (Box Series I-23)
    - Social Workers, 1932; A:092922 (Box Series I-23)
    - Explorers [ Byrd Antarctic Expedition], 1938; A:09293 #1 (Box Series I-23)
  - A:09293 #2 - A:095 (Box Series I-24)
    - Explorers [ Byrd Antarctic Expedition], 1928; A:09293 #2 (Box Series I-24)
    - Explorers [ Byrd Antarctic Expedition], 1928; A:09293 #3 (Box Series I-24)
    - Explorers [ Byrd Antarctic Expedition], 1928; A:09293 #4 (Box Series I-24)
    - Explorers [ Byrd Antarctic Expedition], 1928; A:09293 #5 (Box Series I-24)
    - Explorers [ Byrd Antarctic Expedition II], 1928; A:09293 #6 (Box Series I-24)
    - Athletes, 1909-1917; A:09294 (Box Series I-24)
    - Families of Athletes--R.H. Post, 1931; A:09294 (Box Series I-24)
    - Baseball, 1910-1929; A:092941 (Box Series I-24)
    - Teachers, 1909-1911, 1927-1933; A:093 (Box Series I-24)
    - Politician, n.d.; A:09322 (Box Series I-24)
    - Philosophers and Philosophy Teachers, 1934; A:09327 (Box Series I-24)
    - Fine Arts, Music, 1911; A:0933 (Box Series I-24)
    - Mathematicians, 1910-1911, 1934; A:0934 (Box Series I-24)
    - Astronomers, 1932; A:0935 (Box Series I-24)
    - Naturalists, 1918; A:09371 (Box Series I-24)
    - Psychologists, 1910; A:09376 (Box Series I-24)
    - Scientists, 1928; A:09393 (Box Series I-24)
    - Soldiers, 1918-1919; A:0944 #1 (Box Series I-24)
    - Naval Officers, n.d.; A:0944 #2 (Box Series I-24)
    - Naval Men, 1918-1919; [A:09491] (Box Series I-24)
    - Naval Men, 1907-1918; A:09492 (Box Series I-24)
    - Nursing, 1923-1927; A:0945 (Box Series I-24)
    - Business, 1909-1935; A:095 (Box Series I-24)
  - A:09562 - A:113 (Box Series I-25)
    - Financiers and Democracy in Business, 1907-1923; A:09562 (Box Series I-25)
    - Salesmen and Saleswomen, 1935; A:0957 (Box Series I-25)
    - Boatmen, n.d.; A:0964 (Box Series I-25)
    - Sea Captains, 1908-1920; A:09641 (Box Series I-25)
    - Glass Modeling, 1922; A:09713 (Box Series I-25)
    - Machinists, 1923; A:09732 (Box Series I-25)
    - Dressmakers, 1928; A:09773 (Box Series I-25)
    - Carpenters, 1923-1933; A:0981 (Box Series I-25)
    - Stationary Engineers, 1921; A:09783 (Box Series I-25)
    - Boat Designers, 1938; A:09881 (Box Series I-25)
    - Artists--Abstracts #1 [ fragile], 1828-1936; --- (Box Series I-25)
    - Artists--Abstracts #2 [ fragile], 1828-1936; --- (Box Series I-25)
    - Artists--Abstracts #3 [ fragile], 1828-1936; --- (Box Series I-25)
    - Artists--Abstracts #4 [ fragile], 1828-1936; --- (Box Series I-25)
    - Artists--Abstracts #5 [ fragile], 1828-1936; --- (Box Series I-25)
    - Integumentary System, n.d.; A:1 (Box Series I-25)
    - Ectodermal Dysplasmia, 1929-1933; A:10 (Box Series I-25)
    - Skin, 1919; A:11 (Box Series I-25)
    - Superfluous Skin Growths, 1914; A:1121 (Box Series I-25)
    - Tylosis, 1874-1923; A:113 (Box Series I-25)
  - A:114 - A:13 (Box Series I-26)
    - Keratosis, 1884-1931; A:114 (Box Series I-26)
    - Pecular of Circulation (in Skin), 1925; A:117 (Box Series I-26)
    - Skin Disease, 1913-1934; A:118 (Box Series I-26)
    - Defects of the Skin, 1925; A:119 (Box Series I-26)
    - Pigmentation, 1862-1924; A:12 #1 (Box Series I-26)
    - Skin Color, 1912-1928; A:12 #2 (Box Series I-26)
    - Spotted Skin, 1926-1928; A:1203 (Box Series I-26)
    - Melanism, 1922; A:122 (Box Series I-26)
    - Brunet, 1933; A:1222 (Box Series I-26)
    - Blond, 1923; A:1224 (Box Series I-26)
    - Mulattoes, 1892; A:1225 (Box Series I-26)
    - Albinism [ contains correspondence of Davenport and Laughlin and photos], 1880-1938; A:124 #1 (Box Series I-26)
      - Lillian Mahoney, 1926; A:124-7 (Box Series I-26)
      - Mrs. Robert Roy, 1916; A:124-12 (Box Series I-26)
      - Family affected by albinism, ca. 1938; 1.0 Item(s); Two mounted photographs of an African American family. Three of the children have albinism. (Box Series I-26)
    - Albinism, 1880-1938; A:124 #2 (Box Series I-26)
    - Albinism [ contains correspondence of Davenport and Laughlin], 1908-1913; A:124 #3 (Box Series I-26)
    - Partial Albinism, 1910-1926; A:1242 (Box Series I-26)
    - Xanthism, 1874-1895; A:126 (Box Series I-26)
    - Freckling, 1919-1935; A:127 (Box Series I-26)
    - Other Conditions Due to Disease, 1923; A:128 (Box Series I-26)
    - Papillary Ridges, 1923; A:13 (Box Series I-26)
  - A:131 - A:146 #3 (Box Series I-27)
    - Finger Prints, 1929; A:131 (Box Series I-27)
    - Finger Prints--Jamaica Schoolchildren, 1927; A:131 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hand and Foot Prints, 1917-1925; A:132 and 133 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hair, 1906-1921; A:14 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hypertrichosis, 1909-1928; A:1415 (Box Series I-27)
      - Lionel, Half Man Half Lion at Dreamland Circus Side Show, Coney Island, N.Y., 1928; A:1415-1 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hairlessness and Hypotrichosis, 1848-1925; A:1417 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hair Forms, 1908-1909; A:142 (Box Series I-27)
    - Woolly Hair, 1923; A:1422 (Box Series I-27)
    - Curly Hair, 1919-1935; A:1424 (Box Series I-27)
    - Wavy Hair, 1919-1928; A:1426 (Box Series I-27)
    - Straight Hair, 1919-1920; A:1428 (Box Series I-27)
    - Abnormal Forms of Hair, 1913; A:144 (Box Series I-27)
    - Monilithrix, 1881-1935; A:1442 (Box Series I-27)
    - Silky Hair, 1919; A:1443 (Box Series I-27)
    - Banded Hair, 1930; A:1444 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hair Color, 1907-1926; A:146 #1 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hair Color. Dr. Davenport, 1934; A:146 #2 (Box Series I-27)
    - Hair Color--Training Class Studies, 1911; A:146 #3 (Box Series I-27)
  - A:146 #4 - A:2042 (Box Series I-28)
    - Hair Color, 1913-1919; A:146 #4 (Box Series I-28)
    - Hair Color, 1909-1933; A:146 #5 (Box Series I-28)
    - Black Hair, 1919-1928; A:1461 (Box Series I-28)
    - Dark Hair, 1914-1925; A:1462 (Box Series I-28)
    - Light Hair, 1913-1925; A:1463 (Box Series I-28)
    - White Hair, 1919; A:1464 (Box Series I-28)
    - Red Hair, 1907-1925; A:1465 #1 (Box Series I-28)
    - Red Hair, 1921-1933; A:1465 #2 (Box Series I-28)
    - Dark Red Hair, 1923; A:14652 (Box Series I-28)
    - Hair Darkening with Age, 1919-1924; A:14662 (Box Series I-28)
    - Spottedness (in Hair Color), 1914-1935; A:14668 (Box Series I-28)
    - Graying, 1933; A:1467 (Box Series I-28)
    - Premature Graying, 1913-1935; A:14672 (Box Series I-28)
    - Absence of Gray Hair, 1914, 1928; A:14676 (Box Series I-28)
    - Hirsute Female, 1926, 1927; A:14801 (Box Series I-28)
      - Woman with facial hair, "Missing Link", 1926; A:14801-1 (Box Series I-28)
    - Hair Tuft on Skin, 1919, 1935; A:14803 (Box Series I-28)
    - Scalp, 1934; A:1481 (Box Series I-28)
    - Cow Lick, 1919-1920; A:14812 (Box Series I-28)
    - Eyebrows, 1919-1934; A:14821 (Box Series I-28)
    - Heavy Eyebrows, 1919, 1924; A:148211 (Box Series I-28)
    - Long-Haired Eyebrows, 1919; A:148213 (Box Series I-28)
    - Eyebrows Uniting, 1921, 1933; A:148215 (Box Series I-28)
    - Eyelashes, 1923; A:14822 (Box Series I-28)
    - Double Eyelashes, 1921; A:148227 (Box Series I-28)
    - Heavy Beard, 1929; A:14826 (Box Series I-28)
    - Axillary Hairs, 1933; A:1484 (Box Series I-28)
    - Hairiness of Trunk, 1919; A:1485 (Box Series I-28)
    - Absence of Skin Glands [ contains Laughlin correspondence], 1919; A:1622 (Box Series I-28)
    - Sweat Glands, 1925; A:1641 (Box Series I-28)
    - Mammary Glands, 1924; A:166 (Box Series I-28)
    - Supernumerary Nipples, 1827-1921; A:16624 (Box Series I-28)
    - Tumor of Mammary Glands, 1879; A:16671 (Box Series I-28)
    - Epiphora--Lacryma, 1920; A:1671 (Box Series I-28)
  - A:18 - A:1976 (Box Series I-29)
    - Nails, 1897-1914; A:18 (Box Series I-29)
    - Anomalies of the Nails, 1913-1923; A:181 (Box Series I-29)
    - Leuconychia, 1913-1917; A:1816 (Box Series I-29)
    - Absence of Nails, 1918; A:182 (Box Series I-29)
    - Onycholysis, 1921; A:183 (Box Series I-29)
    - Onychogryposis, 1909-1921; A:184 (Box Series I-29)
    - Other Diseases and Defects of the Nails, 1935; A:189 (Box Series I-29)
    - Congenital Dystrophy of Nails, 1926-1934; A:1891 (Box Series I-29)
    - Allergic Diseases, 1930-1932; A:1905 (Box Series I-29)
    - Acne, 1914-1932; A:191 (Box Series I-29)
    - Seborrhea, 1912; A:1911 (Box Series I-29)
    - Alopecia, 1892-1934; A:192 (Box Series I-29)
    - Spotted Baldness, 1935; A:1923 (Box Series I-29)
    - Baldness--Premature, 1924-1933; A:1926 (Box Series I-29)
    - Eczema, 1869; A:193 (Box Series I-29)
    - Wens, 1925; A:1934 (Box Series I-29)
    - Neurotic Ulcers, 1910-1922; A:1938 (Box Series I-29)
    - Epidermolysis Bullosa, 1886-1927; A:194 (Box Series I-29)
    - Molluscum Fribrosum, 1887-1924; A:19431 (Box Series I-29)
    - Poison Ivy, 1911-1932; A:1942 (Box Series I-29)
    - Gangrene, 1926; A:195 (Box Series I-29)
    - Purpura, 1927-1935; A:19542 (Box Series I-29)
    - Herpes, Fever Blisters, Cold Sores, 1925; A:196 (Box Series I-29)
    - Psoriasis, 1913-1926; A:1962 (Box Series I-29)
    - Pityriasis Rubra, 1910-1924; A:19621 (Box Series I-29)
    - Urticaria (Hives), 1923-1935; A:1963 (Box Series I-29)
    - Erythroderma Exfoliata, 1923; A:1964 (Box Series I-29)
    - Bullous Ichthyosiform Erythroderma, 1926; A:19645 (Box Series I-29)
    - Ichthyosis, 1758-1929; A:1965 (Box Series I-29)